<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Art Archives - Dallas Hidden Gems</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/tag/art/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/</link>
	<description>Explore Dallas Like a Local</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 02:28:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Why We Love These Dallas Attractions!</title>
		<link>https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/2022/05/03/why-we-love-these-dallas-attractions/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=why-we-love-these-dallas-attractions</link>
					<comments>https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/2022/05/03/why-we-love-these-dallas-attractions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dallashiddengemsmain]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 02:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Community]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Garden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/?p=928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As summer approaches, it’s time to start planning vacations and trips! Whether you’re a tourist visiting Dallas or a local who just wants to plan a relaxing day out, we’ve got activities for you to consider! From educational activities to restaurants to fun nights out, we’ve got you covered. Explore Korea town, Deep Ellum, and/or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/2022/05/03/why-we-love-these-dallas-attractions/">Why We Love These Dallas Attractions!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/">Dallas Hidden Gems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As summer approaches, it’s time to start planning vacations and trips! Whether you’re a tourist visiting Dallas or a local who just wants to plan a relaxing day out, we’ve got activities for you to consider! From educational activities to restaurants to fun nights out, we’ve got you covered. Explore Korea town, Deep Ellum, and/or the Star District. We listed great family activities as well as locations where you can take your date! We all get caught up with work and other obligations, so this is an opportunity to take time for yourself. Spending quality time with your family or friends is a great way to destress to re-energize for upcoming obligations.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Learn About Asian Art at Crow Museum of Asian Art</strong></p>



<p>The Crow Museum of Asian Art displayed their first collection, the Trammel and Margaret Crow Collection of Asian Art, in December 1998. This museum features art from China, Japan, India, Korea, and Southeastern Asia. This art museum specifically focuses on celebrating Asian culture and providing an educational experience for visitors. This activity is great for a rainy day and you’ll be able to learn more about Asian art.</p>



<p><strong>Try Swinging a Club at Topgolf Dallas</strong></p>



<p>Topgolf is the perfect activity for a day or night out with friends. This venue is a combination of a golf range, sports bar, and restaurant. Visitors do not have to be experienced in golf at all to have fun. This is a great time to socialize while having fun hitting golf balls. Topgolf’s innovative Toptracer technology tracks the golf balls during games. This allows for fun, competitive games that can be played among friends and family!</p>



<p><strong>Take a Relaxing Walk at Oak Point Park and Nature Preserve&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Feeling stressed and cooped up at home? Oak Point Park and Nature Preserve is a great, low-budget outdoors activity. This park has concrete trails and soft-surface trails in addition to fun water activities. If it’s a hot day, visitors can go kayaking, canoeing, and or paddleboarding. Take time to appreciate nature and nice weather outside. The best part of this outdoor excursion is that it’s free!</p>



<p><strong>Enjoy Beautiful Flowers and Art at the Dallas Arboretum and Botanical Garden</strong></p>



<p>Looking for a change in scenery? The botanic garden’s beautiful blooming flowers is the ideal backdrop for a picnic, stroll, or photoshoot. Not only does this garden have a variety of beautiful plants, it also has an array of sculptures scattered around the arboretum. Are you bringing your children or other family members? No problem! There are plenty of engaging activities to do once you’re inside the garden besides walk around. There are cooking classes and demos and seasonal festivals.</p>



<p><strong>Take a Coffee Break at Cafe Brazil</strong></p>



<p>Do you enjoy your coffee in the morning or are you a college student studying late at night? Cafe Brazil has a Bottomless Coffee bar with a variety of different coffee flavors for you to try. They are open 24 hours 7 days a week which just calls out to all students who stay up to prepare for exams. If you’re hungry, they also have amazing grilled cheeses that compliment their hot chocolate drink!</p>
<div style="text-align:center" class="yasr-auto-insert-visitor"></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/2022/05/03/why-we-love-these-dallas-attractions/">Why We Love These Dallas Attractions!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/">Dallas Hidden Gems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://lloydkwan.github.io/dallashiddengems/2022/05/03/why-we-love-these-dallas-attractions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
